Kun Tian

106 W University Parkway, Apt H2, Baltimore, MD 21210 • 443.824.3257 • ktian1@jhu.edu

Profile

MSF Student, possessing international expertise and diverse internship experience, with a winning track record of achieving business objectives through the use of proven problem solving skills, self-learning skills, precise analysis abilities, constant due diligence and strong business sense.

Education

Master of Science, Finance, Johns Hopkins Carey Business School

Aug 2014

Relevant Coursework: Financial Modeling, Quantitative Financial Analysis,

Risk Management, Advanced Hedge Fund Strategy, M&A

Member, Financial Management Association, Equity Research Association, Investment Banking Club

GPA: 3.31

Bachelor of Accounting, Capital University of Economics and Business

Jul 2012

Relevant Coursework: Financial Accounting, Corporate Finance,

Member, Accounting Forum,

GPA: 3.65

Exchange Student Program, Boston University

Aug 2011- Dec 2011

One of only five Chinese students

Finance Courses: Investment Analysis and Portfolio Management, Personal Finance, Financial Management

GPA: 3.74

Professional Experience

Financial Analyst, Finance and Accounting Department

Jul 2012 - Apr 2013

Novartis Pharma Co. Ltd, Beijing

- Calculated and distributed revenue deduction for hospitals and distributors: bidding compensation, cash discount, price-cut
 compensation, etc.
- · Built up a legal standard guidance for revenue deduction procedure by working with lawyers
- Supported price matrix calculations using excel functions and macros: standardizing input data, adjusting price with required margin, comparing bidding price with gross margin by products by province.
- Transferred old data to new data system and make sure it ran correctly
- · Supported revenue deduction reporting and maintained documentation per internal control requirements
- Improved the customer (internal/external) satisfaction rates for actual revenue deduction in communication and reconciliation process.

Intern, Internal Auditor, Finance Bureau

Apr 2012 – Jun 2012

Ministry of Commerce, People's Republic of China

- Managed bidding process: selected accounting firms and ensured that all the bidding procedures were fair and legal; chose top firm for auditing program
- Participated in the subordinate organization society leaders economic responsibility auditing, and participate in auditing and tracking process of project using fiscal funds
- Collaborated with National Audit Officers in their auditing program in Ministry of Commerce to develop strong relationships between national auditors and officers in Ministry of Commerce in order to make auditing process going smoothly

Intern, Auditing Department

Feb 2012 – Mar 2012

Deloitte, Beijing

- · Implemented annual audit for China Railway Group and handled multiple tasks
- Successfully maintained a good relationship with client personnel
- · Participated in the cash and bank section and provided support for other colleagues, e.g. documentations, cast, review audit report

Qualifications and Exams

Bloomberg Aptitude Test (BAT), 75% percentile

Apr 2014 Oct 2011

GMAT: 690

Additional Information

Skills: Accounting, corporate finance, financial modeling, portfolio management, investments, hedging, risk management

Computer Skills: MatLab, MS Office, Access, SAP, VBA, SPSS, Bloomberg Data System

Languages: Chinese: Mandarin (First language) English: TOEFL (106 out of 120)